[rock music playing]
‎那么…怎么办？到底来不来？
So… what's the deal?
Are we doing this or not?
‎我不知道 我衣服上还写着这种话
I don't know.
‎（够胆 让孩子远离毒品）
I'm literally wearing this.
‎没错 让咱们够胆就试试
Yeah, they're daring us to do it.
‎是啊 他们没考虑清楚
‎别人能解读出啥意思
Yeah, they didn't think
that messaging through.
‎兄弟 这玩意儿算打火机吗？
Bro, does this count as a lighter?
‎算啊
Uh, yeah.
‎我不知道我做不做得来
‎我来自一个有名的家族
I don't know if I can do this.
I'm from a famous family.
‎我表哥给布雷特法弗装过浴室
My cousin did Brett Favre's bathroom.
‎不好意思 别让我又听到
‎布雷特法弗浴室那档子事
I'm sorry. I can't do
your Brett Favre bathroom story again.
‎伙计们 咱们上保健课都学过
Guys, we learned about this
in health class.
‎我觉得大家就应该说…
I think we should just say…
‎哇哦
Whoa.
‎-宝贝 你感觉到了吗？
‎-好像没有
-Babe, are you feeling it?
-I don't think so.
‎大金刚为啥是猩猩 不是驴子？
Why is Donkey Kong
a gorilla and not a donkey?
‎骗人的
It's a lie.
‎他们将整个帝国建立在谎言之上
They based their entire empire on a lie.
‎对啊 我也没啥感觉
Yeah, I'm not feeling it either.
[snaps]
‎有意思
Interesting.
‎伙子 这些旧法兰绒太牛了
Dude, these old flannels are so dope.
‎那些是我爷爷的 他娶了那谁谁
Those are my grandpa's flannels.
He's married to what's-her-name.
‎等等…那是谁来着？
Wait… What's her name?!
‎喂 我是谁？
Hey, who am I?
‎你爷爷的身体
Your grandpa's body. [chuckles]
‎刚才还在 然后没了
It was there. It was gone.
‎就像爱情
Just like love.
‎莉亚 你想知道大金刚的阴谋吗？
Leia, do you want to hear about
the Donkey Kong conspiracy?
‎他是大猩猩
[whispers] He's a gorilla!
‎这有点像雪儿克罗其实不是只乌鸦
It's kinda like how Sheryl Crow
isn't actually a crow.
‎必须的
Totally.
‎爷爷的身体饿了
Grandpa's body's hungry.
‎我去拿零食 你们想吃什么？
I'll get snacks. What do you guys want?
‎葡萄干麦片
Raisin Bran.
[both] Raisin Bran!
‎交给我
On it.
‎等等 我要拿啥来着？
Wait, what was I getting?
‎一 二 三 四…
[young woman] One, two, three, four!
‎在街上闲逛
♪ Hangin' out down the street ♪
‎和上周没什么两样
♪ The same old thing we did last week ♪
‎没什么事好做 就跟你把话说
♪ Not a thing to do but talk to you ♪
‎这样挺好 这样挺好
♪ We're all all right! ♪
‎你好 威斯康辛！
‎（90年代秀）
[young woman] Hello, Wisconsin!
‎我只是…不知道晚上要干点什么了
Well, I just… I don't know
what to do with my evenings anymore
‎这么多夏季重播
with these summer reruns.
‎要能出几集《五口之家》
‎让我弄死一口子都行
I would murder someone
for a fresh Party of Five.
‎要是再让我看一遍《优雅从容》
If I have to sit through
another Grace Under Fire rerun,
‎我就要放火闹事了
I'm gonna root for the fire.
‎凯蒂 我从菜园收了第一轮的菜
Kitty, I've got the first haul
from my vegetable garden.
[Red chuckles]
‎让我们瞧瞧
Show us your harvest.
‎哇！
[laughs] Wow!
[chuckles]
‎我要把它切成片 然后放在汉堡上
I am gonna just slice this up
and put it on some burgers.
‎过家家的汉堡
Doll burgers.
‎-你不在地下室 来这里做什么？
‎-实话实说呗
-What are you doing out of the basement?
-Calling it like I see it.
‎哦 厨房在这里呐 超赞
Oh, here's the kitchen. Wild.
‎嗨！
Hi!
‎可不是嗨了么
Clearly.
‎怎么样…你在楼下
‎跟新朋友玩得开心吗？
So… you having fun downstairs
with your new friends?
‎完全是我想要的
It's everything I've ever wanted.
‎除了葡萄干麦片
Besides Raisin Bran.
‎家里好像没了
Oh, I think we're all out.
‎啊？
What?!
‎但我答应要拿葡萄干麦片的
But I… I promised Raisin Bran.
‎要是没有的话 就又没人跟我玩了
If I don't find some Raisin B,
I'm gonna be alone again!
‎你没事吧？
Are you okay?
‎（菜单）
[upbeat 8-bit video game music playing]
‎谁会不愿意跟你做朋友呢？
Well, now, who wouldn't want
to be your friend?
‎你聪明伶俐
You are smart and charming.
‎说起来 应该给你块饼干吃
In fact, you deserve a cookie.
‎哪个小屁孩要是敢喷你
[Red] If any of those kids give you guff,
‎我非揪着他们衣服领子
I will grab them
by the back of their collar
‎把他们扔出去
‎（加分！）
-and toss them into next week.
-[video game beep]
[chuckles]
‎没错 现在肩膀也好了 他有这本事
That's right. He can do it too,
now that his shoulder is healed.
‎这倒是提醒我了
Which reminds me,
‎你明天能开车送我去做理疗吧？
are you gonna be able to drive me
to physical therapy tomorrow?
‎我要去做头发…但应该能行
Oh. I'm getting my hair done. [laughs]
But I'll make it work.
‎赶紧跟我跳舞吧 大猩猩
Now, dance with me, you big gorilla.
[Red laughs]
‎好吧 聊得好爽
Okay. Good talk.
[rock music playing]
‎-这应该是莉亚的房间
‎-嗯 她人呢？
-I think this is Leia's room.
-Yeah. Where is she?
[Jay] Huh.
‎这睡衣挺朴实的
Pretty sensible sleepwear.
‎不是吧 她有高血压
Oh no. She's got high blood pressure.
‎这是她爷爷奶奶的房间
It's her grandparents' room.
‎现在拿着这件睡衣觉得没意思了
Holding this has become less exciting.
‎挖到宝了！
It's the mother lode!
‎我要下手了
I'm goin' in.
‎宝贝 你穿这件会很好看的
Oh, you'd look so good in this, babe.
‎像是火辣的伐木工
Like a hot lumberjack.
‎惹得我想在小树林跟你干坏事
Makes me wanna do stuff with you
in the woods.
[gulps]
‎我刚支帐篷了
I just pitched a tent.
‎兄弟 有它就不会了
Bro, this will make it go away.
‎这个归我了
This is mine now.
‎原来你们在我爷爷奶奶房间里
Oh, here you guys are.
In my grandparents' room.
‎我都没敢进过这里
The room I've never dared
set foot in my whole life.
‎-我们来这儿没问题吗？
‎-嗯 我没意见
-Is it cool that we're up here?
-Yeah, I'm cool.
‎现在是暑假 大家开开心心
‎想做什么就做什么 对吧？
It's the summer. Let's have fun.
We should do whatever we want. Right?
‎不对
Wrong.
‎-拜拜了
‎-出去
-Buh-bye now.
-Get out.
‎-回头见
‎-出去
-See you soon.
-Get out.
‎-常来啊
‎-出去
-Don't be a stranger.
-Get out.
‎这个糖霜多
Extra icing.
‎那是我的
That was mine.
‎-我们从来不锁推拉门
‎-现在开始要锁了
-We never lock the sliding door.
-We do now.
‎对不起 爷爷
I'm sorry, Grandpa.
‎听着 这种阵仗 我见识过
Look, I lived through this once before.
‎以后要先给你们立点规矩
And I'm not gonna do this again
without some ground rules.
‎告诉你那帮朋友
So you tell your friends,
‎别想吃我的 喝我的
no eating my food, no drinking my drinks,
‎要敢进我房间 我非打他们屁股不可
and if they go in my room,
my foot goes in their ass.
‎人们在卧室里放了各种私人物品
You know, people keep all kinds of
private things in their bedroom.
‎我爸在他们夫妻的房间
‎藏了一条鞭子防贼
My father kept a whip hidden
in my parents' room in case of a burglar.
‎他还有一副毛茸茸的手铐 以防…
Also, he had a pair of furry handcuffs,
in case…
‎我的神啊
Oh dear lord.
‎他们好像觉得我很酷
I think they think I'm cooler than I am.
‎自从我来到这里之后 一切都很棒
Since I got here, it's been amazing.
‎我们抽了…火腿
We smoked…
a ham,
‎还开了…
and we tapped a…
‎火腿
a ham.
‎我担心他们期待还有火腿 知道吗？
I'm worried they're expecting
more ham, you know?
‎这可要不少火腿呢
That's an awful lot of ham.
‎我觉得你给自己太大压力了
Honey, I think you're putting
too much pressure on yourself.
‎何不邀请他们
‎哪天晚上来一起看电影呢？
Why don't you invite them back
for a movie night?
‎没人在听我说话吗？
Is nobody listening to me?
‎奶奶 我不确定
‎电影之夜？不会无聊吗？
I don't know, Grandma.
A movie night? It's not boring?
‎不啊 会很好玩的
No, it'll be fun.
‎就明天吧
We'll do it tomorrow.
‎我们租卷带子 再做一根火腿
We'll rent a movie and make a ham.
‎既然你们心心念念想要
Since you kids are so obsessed with it.
[rock music playing]
‎我去开门！
-[knocking]
-I'll get it!
‎你们哪个冲我家孩子吼来着？
Hey, which one of you yelled at my kids?
‎雷德 找你的
Red, it's for you.
‎我不知道哪个是你家娃 但他们活该
I don't know which ones are yours,
but they deserved it.
‎是格温和内特 谢了 我吼得都烦死了
Oh, that's Gwen and Nate, and thanks.
I'm sick of yelling at them.
‎昨天 我抓到内特在房顶滑旱冰
Yesterday, I caught Nate
on the roof trying on rollerblades.
‎我怀他十个月
I was pregnant with him for ten months.
‎医生说没事 但我觉得够呛
The doctor said it was okay,
but I don't think it was.
‎你搬到隔壁了 是吧？
You moved in next door, right?
‎我上周跟你挥手
‎但你正拿着水管子洗头发 所以…
I waved at you last week, but you were
washing your hair with the hose, so…
‎我叫凯蒂 这位是雷德
[laughs] I am Kitty and this is Red.
‎我是雪莉 是啊 我的淋浴坏了
Oh, I'm Sherri.
And, yeah, my shower head's broke.
‎事实证明
‎它承受不了两个大人的重量
Turns out it can't support
the weight of two fully grown adults.
‎瞧瞧你跟你老公 这么有情趣
Oh, well, look at you and your hubby
keeping things saucy.
‎老公滚蛋了
Oh. Actually, the hubby's
out of the picture,
‎但跟我约会的男人
‎一直吵吵着要一起住
but the guy I've been seeing
is talking about us moving in together.
‎-你们交往多久了？
‎-两个星期
How long have you been seeing each other?
‎-你们交往多久了？
‎-两个星期
Two weeks.
‎刚两个星期 他已经想搬进来了？
Two weeks and he already wants to move in?
‎对 他有点黏人 我应该把他甩了
Yeah, he's kinda clingy.
I should probably break things off.
‎太可惜了 他要啥有啥
‎长得帅 工作好 还有辆蓝色米亚达
It's too bad. He's got it all.
Good looks, good job, blue Miata.
‎你们介意我
‎借用微波炉热一下这个吗？
Hey. You guys mind
if I pop this in your microwave?
‎我家的微波炉 一个钟头都搞不定
It'll take a hour if I use mine.
‎当然 在厨房
Sure, sure. It's in the kitchen.
‎凯蒂 你真贴心 雷德嘛…
Oh. Kitty, you're a sweetheart. And Red…
‎嗯
Yeah.
‎她的包里什么都有
She has all sorts of things in that bag.
‎是啊 垃圾一满兜
Yeah, she's like a trashy Mary Poppins.
[rock music playing]
‎也许你想太多了
Maybe you're overthinking this.
‎我们能快进到你选电影的环节吗？
Could we fast-forward
to the part where you pick a movie?
Oh! [laughing]
‎“快进”！真妙
"Fast-forward"! That is clever!
‎我应该把这段子寄去《雷诺今夜秀》
I should send that in to Leno.
‎关键是我不能挑
‎大家都觉得傻乎乎的片子
It's really important I don't pick
something everyone will think is dorky.
‎你选的才不会傻乎乎呢
Well, you couldn't pick something dorky
if you tried.
‎-来吧 你最喜欢哪部电影？
‎-《威鲸闯天关》吧
-Come on. What's your favorite movie?
-Um, I guess Free Willy.
‎妈呀 傻冒泡儿了！
Whoa. Dork city!
[laughs]
[grunts]
‎我去找人帮忙
I'm gonna go ask for some help.
‎-举起手来！
‎-要钱拿走 全拿走
-Stick 'em up!
-Aah! Take my money! Take everything!
‎我老板从来不锁车
‎她的车牌上写着“刷片荡妇”
My boss never locks her car!
Her license plate says MOVIESLUT!
‎是很难听 我也不想说
‎就是告诉你一声
I know. I don't want to say it.
I'm just letting you know.
‎求你了…
Please…
‎杰伊 是我啦 逗你玩呢
Jay, it's just me. I was joking.
‎哦
Oh. Yeah.
[clears throat]
‎我也是
Me too. [sniffles]
‎真够逗的
Good one.
‎没想到你在这里打工
-I, um, didn't know you worked here.
-Oh.
‎混演艺圈这事 我不想太高调
Well, I didn't want to brag about
being in show business.
‎对哈
Right. Um…
‎我想为电影之夜选一部酷酷的电影
So I'm trying to find
a cool movie for movie night,
‎我也不是超级担心啦
and, not that I'm super worried about it
or anything,
‎那是哪部片子来着？
but what's that one movie?
‎就一群人 在那里 那谁谁的？
You know, with all the guys
and the place and… the guys?
‎-《疯狂店员》？
‎-对的 《疯狂店员》！
-Uh, Clerks?
-Clerks, yes!
‎我去！我超爱《疯狂店员》
‎凯文史密斯 多棒啊？
Get out! I love Clerks.
Kevin Smith, right?
‎就是 他在里面超性感的
Oh yeah! He was so sexy in that.
‎哦 好吧
Okay. Cool.
‎我看看有没有哈 看看…
Uh, well, let's see if I have it.
Let's see…
‎好烦 租出去了
Ah, crud, it's out.
‎有人霸占六个星期没还呢
Some guy has had it for six weeks.
‎杰伊 来厕所帮我一下
Yo, Jay. I need your help in the bathroom.
‎《魔岛仙踪》的火山喷了
It's a Joe Versus the Volcano situation.
‎回头聊 妹子
Later, girl.
‎-来吧 奶奶 我们得走了
‎-等一下
-Come on, Grandma. We gotta go.
-Oh, just a sec.
‎戴夫牧师 是我 凯蒂！
‎（只限成人）
Pastor Dave, it's Kitty!
‎上次百乐餐之后就没再见你呢
I haven't seen you since the potluck.
‎这也太不圣洁了
That was very unholy.
[rock music playing]
‎嗨 福尔曼先生
Hey, Mr. Forman.
‎看看我在你的迷你菜园里发现了什么
Look what I found
in your garden of tiny vegetables.
‎小黄瓜
Baby cucumber.
‎给我
Give me that.
‎这是正常尺寸
That is normal-sized.
‎别觉得丢脸
‎也许它只是蔫巴了 还没硬起来
Don't be embarrassed.
Maybe it's a grower, not a shower.
‎说起来
‎我是来找你聊聊法兰绒衬衣的事
Anyway, I came by
to talk to you about your flannels.
‎能给我一件吗？
Can I have one?
‎为啥？
Why?
‎我女朋友说我穿着可帅
‎其实我有点高攀不上她
My girlfriend said I looked good in it,
and she's kinda out of my league.
‎但我非常爱她 我想让她开心
But I love her so much,
and I want to keep her happy.
‎真不错
That's sweet.
‎我和第一任女友也有过类似经历
I had a similar thing
with my first girlfriend.
‎你知道她叫什么吗？
You know what her name was?
‎出去
Get out.
‎遵命 先生
Yes, sir.
‎嘿 邻居
Hey, neighbor.
‎凯蒂说我家淋浴修好之前
Kitty said until I get
my shower situation fixed,
‎我可以来这里搓搓洗洗
I can rinse my nooks and crannies
over here.
‎这里也是我家
Well, this is my house too.
‎回你自己家搓搓洗洗去
So you can just take your crannies home.
‎我还得借把剃刀
I'm gonna need to borrow a razor too.
‎蓝色米亚达约我去“胡塞餐厅”吃晚餐
Blue Miata is taking me
to dinner at Houlihan's.
‎有人愿意在“胡塞餐厅”花大钱
‎你可得把毛毛刮干净
When a guy springs for Houlihan's,
you gotta whack the weeds.
[rock music playing]
‎你确定我们可以
Are you sure it's okay
‎就这么闯进别人家要录像带哇？
that we're just showing up
at somebody's house to get a movie?
‎奶奶 我别无选择
I'm out of options here, Grandma.
‎如果我们被杀怎么办？
‎谁惦记着给慢炖锅关火啊？
What if we get murdered?
Who's gonna turn off the Crock-Pot?
-[doorbell chimes]
-[Kitty sighs]
‎老天！
Aw, man!
‎万圣节又来搞偷袭了
Halloween snuck up on me again.
‎听着 我可没什么糖块
Hey, listen. I don't have any candy, man,
‎但我有几根火柴
‎还有一张1975年的停车票
but I do have some matches
‎但我有几根火柴
‎还有一张1975年的停车票
and a parking ticket from 1975.
‎利奥 嗨
Leo. Hi.
‎你不认得我了吗？
Don't you recognize me?
‎认得
I do.
‎对呀 你打扮得像凯蒂
‎有房子有头发那个女的
Yeah. You're dressed like Kitty,
the lady with the house and the hair.
‎这身打扮绝了
Killer costume, man.
‎你是不是租了电影《疯狂店员》
‎而且没有还？
Did you rent the movie Clerks
and not return it?
‎你们是警察吗？
Are you guys cops?
‎利奥 集中注意力
Leo, focus.
‎你们如果要找利奥集中注意力
Hey, if you cops are looking
for Leo Focus,
‎那你们找错人了
you got the wrong guy, man.
‎拜托 利奥 这很重要
Please, Leo. This is important.
‎知道我最近喜欢刷啥片子不？
You know what I've been watching
a ton of lately?
‎《真实世界》
The Real World.
‎想想看
Because think about it.
‎如果他们演的是真实世界
‎那这些又是啥？
If that's the real world, what's all this?
‎这法子可能行不通
This might be a dead end.
‎等等 利奥 今天就是万圣节
Wait. Leo, it is Halloween.
‎你知道我想要的其实是什么吗？
And you know what I really want
instead of candy?
‎《疯狂店员》的录影带
The movie Clerks.
‎我勒个去！我正好有一卷
Crazy! I got a copy.
‎我去拿
I'll get it for you.
‎-等等 你怎么认识这个人的？
‎-他只是…他很…
-Wait. So how do you know this guy?
-Oh, he just… He's…
‎就那样啦 他就是
It's the usual.
You know, he's an older man
‎你爸和他朋友年轻时候
‎经常一起玩的老家伙
who used to hang out with your dad
and his friends when they were teenagers.
‎不会的
Nah.
‎有事儿他们会出声的
They would have said something.
‎好了 你们就是要录影带的警察？
Okay, are you the cops
looking for a movie?
‎对 没错
Yes, we are.
‎-万圣节快乐
‎-谢谢
-Happy Halloween, man.
-Thank you. Thank you.
‎原来你在这儿呢
There you are.
‎莉亚和我一下午可开心了
Leia and I had such a fun afternoon.
‎凯蒂 咱们家被袭击了
Kitty, this house is under attack.
‎到处都是半大小孩儿
There are teenagers everywhere
‎还有一个半裸女在我家到处招摇
and a half-naked lady
swinging her bits around my house.
‎太好了 雪莉来洗澡了
Oh good. Sherri's using the shower.
‎你怎么又找人来家里捣乱？
Why did you open our house to chaos again?
‎原本好好的 笨蛋都滚蛋了！
We had it made.
All the dumbasses were gone!
‎我有点想念他们
Well, I miss them.
‎雷德 我感觉家里太安静了
It's been too quiet
around here for me, Red.
‎那就养只鹦鹉
Well, then, get a parrot!
‎如果还嫌不够聒噪 就把你姐妹叫来
And if that's not enough squawkin'
for you, invite your sister.
‎我挺享受莉亚来过暑假的
I like having Leia visit for the summer.
‎家里又有生气了
The house is alive again.
‎那天 我进厕所一看
‎有人尿完没放马桶盖
The other day, I walked into the bathroom,
someone had tinkled, left the seat up,
‎把我给高兴坏了
and it made me so happy.
‎我可以帮忙啊
I could do that for you!
‎随你怎么抱怨 但过去几个星期
Complain all you want,
but these past few weeks
‎我又看到了雷德从前的影子
I have seen glimpses of the old Red.
‎那种火焰 那种激情 我很想念他
The fire, the passion. I miss him.
‎他退休了
He's retired.
‎但他还活着
But he's still alive.
‎你不能一整天
You can't spend all day
‎都在园子里鼓捣番茄
scraping around in your garden,
playing with your tomatoes.
‎-你喜欢我的番茄！
‎-你的番茄太小了！
-You love my tomatoes!
-Your tomatoes are small!
‎你头上全是汗
Your head is sweaty.
‎你的胸口起伏得厉害
-Your chest is heaving.
-[Kitty moans]
["Tell Me Something Good"
by Chaka Khan playing]
♪ Tell me something good… ♪
‎看来退休的日子结束了
Well, so much for a quiet retirement.
‎管道很久没进毛刷刷了
There's no more lint in my dryer filter.
[both laughing]
‎我现在出来安全不？
Is it safe to come out?
‎雪莉
Sherri.
‎我正洗澡呢 刚完事 你俩就开始折腾
I was taking a shower. When I got done,
you guys were dirty doggin' it,
‎我就在里面窝着 等暴风雨结束
so I just hunkered down
and rode out the storm.
‎我就说听见冲马桶的声音了
I told you I heard the toilet flush.
‎抱歉 我就是上来梳洗
‎准备赴一场不该赴的约会
Sorry, I was only up here 'cause I was
getting ready for this mistake of a date.
‎约会？
A date?
‎蓝色米亚达 胡塞…要跟上剧情呀
Blue Miata, Houliha… Keep up.
‎我倒是难得有这种机会思考
But it did give me time to think,
which I never get to do.
‎我到底想要什么？
I mean, what do I want from my life?
‎因为我确定
Because I'm pretty sure
‎躲在邻居家浴室听老头老太嘿咻
‎可不是我的追求
hiding in my neighbor's bathroom
listening to old people bang isn't it.
‎听着像别人啃玉米棒子
Sounded like somebody was eating
corn on the cob.
‎我是怎么了？
What's wrong with me?
‎为什么我总是不断犯同样的错误？
Why do I keep making the same mistake
over and over?
‎哦 亲爱的 别这么难为自己
Oh, honey. Go easy on yourself.
‎你有一份稳定的工作
You have a steady job.
‎你一个人养育了两个好孩子
You are raising two wonderful kids
all on your own.
‎你很棒
You are amazing.
‎-凯蒂 你为什么要骗她？
‎-雷德…
-Kitty, why are you lying to her?
-Red…
‎但他没得说错
But he's not wrong.
‎或许可以先把男人放在一边
Okay, maybe it's time
to take a break from the fellas
‎体验一下独立的感觉
and see what it's like on your own.
‎孤身一人 感觉好可怕
Being alone sounds scary.
‎你不是一个人 你还有我们
Well, you're not alone. You've got us.
‎我们？
Us?
‎你现在心情应该好点了吧
You'd think you'd be
in a better mood right now.
[rock music playing]
‎欢迎来到电影之夜
Welcome to movie night.
‎今晚肯定超赞 首先
It's gonna be pretty major,
so to kick things off right
‎我给你们每人准备了一盒葡萄干麦片
I got everyone
their own box of Raisin Bran.
‎葡萄干麦片！
Raisin Bran! Raisin Bran!
Raisin Bran! [chuckles]
‎大家都喜欢 记得吗？
Everybody loves it. Remember?
‎不是吗？这事没发生吗？
No? Did that not happen?
‎你知道谁喜欢葡萄干麦片吗？
‎我表哥 他给布雷特法弗…
Oh, you know who loves Raisin Bran?
‎你知道谁喜欢葡萄干麦片吗？
‎我表哥 他给布雷特法弗…
My cousin who did Brett Favre's--
‎别
Do not.
‎-那我们要看什么？
‎-我最喜欢的电影
-So what are we watching?
-Uh, my favorite movie.
‎《疯狂店员》凯文史密斯主演
‎我可喜欢他了
Clerks, starring Kevin Smith.
‎《疯狂店员》凯文史密斯主演
‎我可喜欢他了
[chuckles] I'll take a slice of that.
‎好吧…
[both] Okay…
‎嗨 音乐电视台 我是利奥
Hey, MTV. I'm Leo, man.
‎我今年74了
I'm 74 years young,
‎演《真实世界》特别合适
and I'd be perfect
for The Real World, man.
‎这是什么呀？
What's this?
‎不知道 应该是《疯狂店员》才对
I don't know.
It was supposed to be Clerks.
‎说到个人趣事
Fun facts about me.
‎我从过山车上摔下来三回
I've fallen off of
three roller coasters, man.
‎其实是四回 如果算上第四回
Well, four, if you count the fourth one.
[TV clicks off]
‎还是别看了
Uh… forget movies.
‎有人有趣事分享吗？
Does anyone have
any funny stories to share?
[choking]
‎很好 内特
Oh good, Nate.
‎不 他吃葡萄干麦片噎着了 太干了
No. He's choking on the Raisin Bran.
It's too dry.
‎给他拿点喝的
Give him something to drink.
‎不用吸管了！
Forget the straw!
‎好了 宝贝 喝吧
Okay. Drink, baby, drink.
[slurping]
‎好了 顺下去了
I'm good. It went down.
[choking]
‎不行 你得这样 清出来…
No, you gotta clear it out like this.
Like…
‎不行 你得这样 清出来…
-[coughs]
‎莉亚 你应该当活动策划人
‎这真是太有意思了
Leia, you should be an event planner.
This is so fun.
‎对不起！
Gah! I'm sorry!
‎我真的希望今晚能完美
I really wanted this
to be a perfect night.
‎算了
[scoffs] Forget it.
‎莉亚…
Leia…
‎别吃了
Hey, stop eating that.
‎我饿了
I'm hungry!
‎嘿 戏精 刚才怎么回事？
Yo, drama queen. What was up with that?
‎我太假了
I'm a fraud.
‎我根本没看过《疯狂店员》
I've never even seen Clerks.
‎我最喜欢的电影是…《威鲸闯天关》
My favorite movie is… Free Willy.
‎讲的是一个小男孩
It's about a boy.
‎还有他的鲸鱼
And his whale.
‎然后呢？
So?
‎他想把鲸鱼送回大海
So he tries to get Willy
back in the ocean.
‎不 我是想问 你为什么那么激动？
No. I mean,
why did you melt down in there?
‎就是…
It's just…
‎我感觉跟你们在一起 我很格格不入
I feel like an imposter in this group.
‎你们那么酷 那么要好
You guys are all so close and so cool,
‎只有我
and I'm just me.
‎如果你怀疑自己 记住
If you're ever doubting yourself,
just remember,
‎你家地下室超赞的
you have a killer basement.
‎我还以为你会说些更好听的呢
I thought you were gonna say
something way nicer.
‎你知道这里有多无聊吗？
You know how boring it is around here?
‎上礼拜 我们往河里扔了一根棍子
‎然后朝它扔别的棍子
Last week, we threw a stick in the creek
and tried to hit it with other sticks.
‎内特管这叫“棒打棒棒”
Nate called it Stick Stick.
‎傻瓜 不光是你家地下室
It's not just about your basement, dummy.
‎如果是我让你有压力 咱们俩好得很
If you're stressing about me, we're good.
‎如果你担心自己不合群
And if you're worried about
fitting in with everyone else,
‎那你算找到不合群的人了
you found the people who don't fit in.
‎我可是个中王者
And I am their queen.
‎我没交过像你这样的朋友
Never had a friend like you.
‎我知道
I know.
‎伙计们！
Guys!
‎我们在这个袋子里又找到另一个袋子
We just found another bag inside this bag.
‎袋中袋
Bag bag!
‎我刚想到的
I just came up with that.
[rock music playing]
‎袋中袋里可真有好货
The stuff in that bag bag was good good.
‎那也比不过《威鲸闯天关》我喜欢
Not as good as Free Willy. I love it.
‎冷静 这就是
‎鲸鱼版《ET外星人》而已
Check yourself.
This is just E.T. with a whale.
‎虽然不是《疯狂店员》
‎但也挺可爱的 对吧？
I know it's not Clerks,
but it's kinda cute, right?
‎就好像我是那个男孩
‎鲸鱼威利是橡皮筋
It's like… I'm the boy
‎就好像我是那个男孩
‎鲸鱼威利是橡皮筋
and Willy's the rubber band.
‎我终于懂了
I get it now.
‎莉亚 威利会成功吗？
Leia, is Willy gonna make it?
‎ET外星人成功了吗？
Did E.T. make it?
‎-加油 威利
‎-加油
-Come on, Willy.
-Come on.
‎你能行
You can do it.
‎-你能行 来吧
‎-好的 威利
-You got this. Come on.
-Yes, Willy.
‎耶！
[all] Yeah!
‎他成功了！
He made it!
-[movie score swells]
-[laughing]
‎就当没发生
This never happened.
‎嗨 福尔曼先生
Hey, Mr. Forman.
‎这是我在面包车里发现的
I found this in my van.
‎看来我有一个神秘的仰慕者
Looks like I have a secret admirer.
‎是你 对吧？
[whispers] It's you, isn't it?
‎不过是一件衬衣 别搞得这么诡异
It's just a shirt. Don't make it weird.
‎我没有
I'm not.
‎-我能叫你雷德叔叔吗？
‎-出去
-Can I call you Uncle Red?
-Get out.
‎再见 雷德叔叔
Bye, Uncle Red.
‎凯蒂
Kitty.
‎你就穿这身跟男人分手？
That's what you're wearing
to break up with a guy?
‎那泳池派对得穿成什么样啊
I can't imagine
what you would wear to a pool party.
‎说什么呢？这是我的葬礼装
What? This is my funeral outfit.
‎这是跟别人道永别的衣裳
It's what I wear
to say goodbye to someone forever.
[car horn honking]
‎肯定是他了 老天 我好紧张
That's him. Oh God, I'm just so nervous.
‎我吃了一堆头发
I've eaten a ton of my hair.
‎之前比现在高多了
This was so much higher.
‎别这样
Well, stop that.
‎-你很坚强
‎-嗯
-You are strong.
-Yeah.
‎-你很独立
‎-嗯
-You're independent.
-Yeah.
‎-你还年轻…吧
‎-嗯
You're still young…
‎-你还年轻…吧
‎-嗯
-Yeah.
-…ish.
‎-他也就有一个高级喇叭
‎-嗯
-He is just some guy with a fancy horn.
-Right.
‎好了 去吧
Now, go.
‎甩掉那家伙！
Dump that chump!
‎《瑞奇莱克》节目上就这么说
That's what they say on Ricki Lake.
[laughs]
‎我想着让你看看我的性感样
‎应该挺不赖的
I thought it would be fun
for you to see me look this sexy.
[rock music playing]
‎字幕翻译：Zeo Niu